http://www.srpsubro.com/privacy.php

Subrogation Pricing
Receive a Letter?
Subrogation Pricing
Receive a Letter?
CONTACT
RECEIVE A LETTER?
PRICING
Privacy Statement
Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our on-line information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiable.
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself to us on the Strategic Recovery Partnership Inc. site (the 'Site') when subscribing only to help answer your inquiries and provide solutions, or for security purposes. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to answer your inquiries and provide solutions or to enforce security.
We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive and to provide you with periodic updates and information about Strategic Recovery Partnership. These addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties, except as necessary for security purposes. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our web site. For example, we may tell an affiliate that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our web site, or that X number of people filled out our registration form, but we will not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
The Site employs cookies to recognize you and your access privileges on the Site, as well as to track site usage. Subscribers who do not accept cookies from the domain "srpsubro.com" may not be able to access some areas of the Site on the Web.
Strategic Recovery Partnership may perform statistical analyses of user behavior in order to study interest in various areas of the Site (for services development purposes). In these statistical analyses we will disclose information to third parties only in aggregate form. Personal information about you as an individual will not be provided to any third party without your consent.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us on-line in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity first to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
If you participate in a Forum or other Service on the Site, any information you disclose when posting a message in a Forum becomes public. Thus, if you post a message in a Forum or on a Service you are making your e-mail address available to others, which could result in unsolicited e-mail from other subscribers or parties.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, legal and other procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Opting-Out and Corrections
Strategic Recovery Partnership will a) Remove you and your personal information, from our database, thereby canceling your registration; b) Correct personal information that you state is erroneous; or c) Permit you to "opt out" of further e-mail contact (excepting notification of major changes to the service) while still allowing access to the site.
How to Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
© 1993 - 2020 Strategic Recovery Partnership Inc.855.557.5777
|
Privacy
About SRP
Since 1993, SRP has focused on maximizing recoveries, generating client revenue, leveraging state-of-the-art technology, and providing unlimited legal support for subrogation cases and recovery opportunities, consistently achieving a proven revenue stream for TPA's and health plans.
